bestmobileworld.com 2014-04-12

# Privacy Policy | Tech Blog - Best Mobile World

**Privacy Policy:**  
Google as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
We don’t request or save any personal information including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address.

We also use third party advertisements on our site to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.This is generally used for geo targeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).  
Log Files:  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.  
Updated on April 04,2009  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  
**Third Party Cookies:**  
In the course of serving advertisements, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

Rating: 9.0/ **10** (1 vote cast)

Privacy Policy, 9.0 out of 10 based on 1 rating
